// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The estimated population of the Amish of North America as of June 2018 is:', 
      a: '415,000', 
      b: '330,000',
      c: '510,000',
      d: '190,000',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is an illegal activity the Amish have been investigated for?', 
      a: 'Puppy mills', 
      b: 'Amish-to-Amish hate crimes',
      c: 'Drunk driving',
      d: 'All of the above',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'One of the main goals for teenagers on Rumspringa is: ', 
      a: 'To party and experience non-Amish fun', 
      b: 'To find a spouse',
      c: 'To try out other religions',
      d: 'To find a job outside of the community',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'A common sign you may see when visiting the Amish community asks to please not:', 
      a: 'Use cell phone', 
      b: 'Take photos',
      c: 'Play music',
      d: 'Be barefoot',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What celebrity grew up Amish?', 
      a: 'Mini Me', 
      b: 'Carrot Top',
      c: 'Tilda Swinton',
      d: 'Jenny McCarthy',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'The average American adult takes about 4,000 steps a day. The average Amish man takes about:', 
      a: '16,985', 
      b: '23,895 ',
      c: '18,425',
      d: '26,700',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'What will you NOT see on a married Amish man?', 
      a: 'Beard', 
      b: 'Black plain hat ',
      c: 'Dark colored suit',
      d: 'Mustache',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following IS allowed in Amish communities', 
      a: 'Washing machines', 
      b: 'Musical nstruments',
      c: 'Dancing',
      d: 'Fingertip length skirts',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'The ______ is considered the  unwritten manual to Amish society:', 
      a: 'Fruhstuck', 
      b: 'Grundsatzen',
      c: 'Ausbund',
      d: 'Ordnun',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Ozzys middle name is...', 
      a: 'Yoder', 
      b: 'Jebediah',
      c: 'Ezekiel',
      d: 'Crouton',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};